Wonderful.
좋아요
Where we left off is we had just created the Get Features function, which builds our features dictionary
멈춘 곳에서 기능 Get 기능을 만들었죠 4가지 기능으로 기능 사전을 만드는
with our four features.
거예요
Let's look at one so we can call get features for let's say our initial training point.
한 번 보죠 기능을 get 요청해 초기 훈련 지점을 호출하는 거예요
And what we get back is this nice little this little dictionary.
Get을 누르면 이 멋진 사전이 나와요
Apparently it's £2.2 in its weight.
2파운드예요 무게로 2kg이에요
That's its average rank.
그게 평균 등급이죠
That's the length of the text.
텍스트의 길이예요
And it is not a top electronics brand.
일류 전자 제품 브랜드도 아니고요
So these become the rather meager features that we have engineered.
그래서 우리가 만든 건 다소 빈약한 형태가 됐죠
You can do better and I challenge you to do so.
더 잘할 수 있어요 더 잘하도록 해요
All right.
좋아요
Now it's time for some machine learning.
이제 머신 러닝을 할 거예요
There's this little utility function that's going to take a list of items and convert it into a dataframe.
항목 목록을 데이터 프레임으로 변환하는 유틸리티 함수가 있어요
A pandas dataframe.
팬더스 데이터 프레임이에요
Not going to go through this in detail, because this is not a course about traditional machine learning.
자세히 설명하진 않겠습니다 전통적인 머신 러닝 과목이 아니니까요
If you know DataFrames and you'll be familiar with this, and we use this to make a training dataframe
데이터 프레임에 대해 잘 아신다면 훈련 데이터와 테스트 데이터 프레임에
and a test dataframe, just picking the top 250 points in our test data set.
사용합니다 테스트 데이터 세트에서 상위 250포인트를 고르는 거죠
So there we go.
자, 됐어요
We've made our conversion and now this is the business.
변환 작업을 했고 이제 비즈니스가 시작됐어요
This is where we run traditional linear regression.
전통적인 선형 회귀를 실행하는 곳이죠
We set our features.
특징을 설정하죠
Um we specify the names of the columns of our features.
기능의 열 이름을 지정해요
This is where all the action happens.
모든 액션이 일어나는 곳이죠
Model equals linear regression is saying we want a linear regression model.
모델 = 선형 회귀는 우리가 선형 회귀 모델을 원한다는 뜻이죠
And then we fit that model to our x values, our features and our y values is the actual prices of our
그 모델을 엑스 값, 기능, y 값에 맞추는 건 훈련 데이터 집합의 실제 가격이에요
And that this this is where the action happens and where the model is actually fit.
여기서 액션이 일어나고 모델이 실제로 맞는 거죠
Then going to print the the features and their coefficients or how much weight they got.
그런 다음 특징과 계수 무게를 출력하죠
So we can see that and get a sense of how important were each of our features.
그걸 보면서 각 특징이 얼마나 중요한지 알 수 있죠 get get get get it
And then we will actually run a prediction on that test set and get things like the, the MSE, the
그런 다음 테스트 세트에서 예측을 실행합니다 평균 제곱 에러와 R 제곱을 얻기
mean squared error and the r squared for for the data scientists amongst you that want to have a look
위해서요 여러분 중 데이터 과학자들이 그걸 보고 싶어 하니까요
at that.
하지만 걱정 마세요, 곧 보게 될 테니까요 우리가 전에 만든 프레임워크를 이용해서요
That's going to show it on the same graph.
같은 그래프에 나타나요
So make your guess where you think this is going to come out compared to the average model.
평균 모델과 비교해서 어디서 나올지 추측해 보세요
Let's quickly look back at the average model to remind ourselves what we're trying to beat.
우리가 이기려고 하는 걸 상기시키기 위해 평균 모델을 잠깐 보죠
So an average guess has an error of 145 $146.
평균 오차는 145달러 146센트죠
So hopefully linear regression can do better than average.
선형 회귀가 평균보다 나아졌으면 좋겠어요
Let's see.
어디 보죠
Let's first run it.
일단 해 보죠
It's quick.
금방 끝나요
Uh, so the different uh, um coefficients, the weights that it gave things, you can see that how
계수와 무게에 따라 무게가 달라지면 무게가 작아지다가
heavy something is gets a small uh, positive weight.
양극이 되는 걸 알 수 있어요
How it ranks gets a larger one.
순위가 더 커졌어요
The text length is very small signal very low.
텍스트 길이가 아주 작고 신호도 아주 낮아요
Is it a top electronics brand?
최고의 전자제품 브랜드인가요?
Makes a big difference.
큰 차이가 있죠
Things that are top electronics brands get a lot.
톱 전자 제품은 많이 받아요 Get it
Um, okay, so now, uh, we simply wrap this in a function because this is what we're going to use
이제 이걸 함수로 래핑할 거예요 이걸 테스트용 시각화기에 사용할
in our cool test visualizer.
거거든요
We wrap it in a function called linear regression Pricer.
선형 회귀 프라이서라는 함수로 감싸요
And we will then just use we will it passes in an item.
그런 다음 우린 그냥∙∙∙ 항목을 전달하죠
We will get the features for that item.
해당 아이템의 기능을 get 할 거예요
We will then convert that to a data frame.
그걸 데이터 프레임으로 변환할 거예요
And then we will call our linear regression model to predict where that comes.
그런 다음 선형 회귀 모델을 불러 어디서 올지 예측하죠
And let's see what happens.
어떻게 되는지 보죠
Tester dot test.
테스터요, 점 테스터
Linear regression Pricer.
선형 회귀 프라이저예요
Are you ready for this.
마음의 준비 됐어요?
Remember what the average number was.
평균을 기억하세요
Here we go.
시작할게요
Oh, uh, execute the cell before.
그 전에 감옥을 실행해요
Uh, how many times have I done that now?
제가 몇 번이나 그랬죠?
Bam!
좋아요!
Well, we can see the colors.
색깔이 보이네요
We can see that it's got a lot of reds in there, but maybe some more greens than before.
붉은색이 많이 보이는데 전보다 녹색이 더 많아요
Maybe it hasn't done terribly.
그렇게 끔찍하진 않았을 거예요
It's getting some things right.
제대로 하고 있어요
Let's see.
어디 보죠
Well, there we have it.
자, 다 됐어요
It's only done a little bit better than the average.
평균보다 약간 더 비트 박스가 잘 나왔어요
Only a little bit better.
비트보다 조금 더 낫네요
And indeed if you look at the results you can see that basically there's a small increase here, but
실제로 결과를 보시면 기본적으로 여기에 약간 증가한 것을 볼 수 있습니다. 하지만
it's clustered Stood around the average kind of point, with some of the points coming in about $200
평균 점 부근에 클러스터되어 있습니다. 어떤 점들은 약 200달러 더 증가하고요.
And guess what?
그거 알아요?
Those are going to be the ones where is electronics brand is is is true is top electronics brand.
전자 제품 브랜드가 최고라는 걸 보여주는 제품들이 될 거예요
Uh, and so they got a little uplift which did well for this one point here.
그래서 약간 들뜬 상태였고 한 시점에서 잘 풀렸어요
But otherwise uh, didn't particularly work out well for the model.
하지만 그 외에는 모델에게 도움이 되지 않았어요
Uh, so it tried its best.
최선을 다했어요
It got a, uh, 139, um, uh, error.
139... 에러가 났네요
And it, it it had a hit.
그리고 히트 쳤죠
It was green, uh, almost 16% of the time.
16% 정도는 녹색이었어요
So that's our linear regression model.
이게 우리 선형 회귀 모델이에요
You can do better.
더 잘할 수 있잖아요
Come on in.
들어오세요
Now, engineer some features.
이제 기능을 설계해 보죠
I know it's not new.
새롭진 않죠
Uh, great.
좋아요
LM data science, but it's really good to build this foundational knowledge and doing some old school
기본 지식을 쌓는 것도 좋지만 구식 기능 공학도
And besides, it's going to make it all the more satisfying when we start working with LMS and see how
게다가 LMS로 작업을 시작하면 훨씬 더 만족스러울 겁니다 어떻게 되는지
they do.
보죠
So come on in there, build some features, see how you do.
들어가서 기능들을 만들어 보세요
But next time we're going to, uh, look at some more sophisticated baseline models.
하지만 다음 시간에는 좀 더 정교한 기본 모델을 살펴볼 거예요
I will see you then.
그때 봐요